Yay!
Onigiri
Yoo-hoo!
I wanna see inside!
Cute seatbelt that's failing.
Seat belt.
Seat belt
Seat pockets
There is one
Eight hours.
I brought it with me.
Popillo
Cute.
I can't see him yet.
We'll be waiting for you.
Yoo-hoo!
Indonesia Indonesia
Indonesia-Indonesia.
No?
Aharru.
Aharru, sorry, Indonesia, is that him? Is it there? Oh, there it is!
Oh, yes!
Okay.
Let's go! Let's go!
There they go!
Good night Indonesia, good night Indonesia, good night Indonesia.
Good night.
Good night, good night, good night.
Good night good night
Good night Good night Good night
Good night, ma'am.
Good night.Good night.
Good night.
Good night
Good night, good night.
Yeah, it's kind of tall over there.
The tower is so beautiful.
I'm in the same room as Kanami.
Same room!
Always.
For 6 days.
Yeah, six days.
Six days together.
Don't hate me.
Yesterday we were talking about it, and Ramen said...
I'm not going to be clean. I'll be fine.
I'll be with you 24/7 for 6 days. What was it? Aquamacan? Aquamacan?
Aqua aqua aqua aqua.
Aqua, aqua, aqua, aqua.
Aqua aqua aqua aqua aqua aqua aqua aqua aqua aqua aqua
Bon appétit, I'm hungry, I'm hungry, good morning
Good morning
I think it's a little humid.
Not so different from Japan?
I thought it was different at night.
Yeah...
It's a very rainy season anyway.
It's always been the rainy season.
I wonder if it's here.
I think it's here.
Trompas az Hjorin, please call me Hjorin.
The water is huge!
It's big enough for an airplane!
Hey, little guy!
Cute!
Aww, Usamu, you're so cute, so cute, so cuteAww, Usamu, you're so cute... cute, cute, cute.
Indonesian sweets.
Hey, guys.
They're all here.
It's like sushi.
So cute!
Cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute!
Ta-da-da-da!
What's that?
I want to know what it tastes like.
But it smells so good.
Here, you know what it is? It's a little hard.
It's hard.
Well, how about you, Akichan?
Steamed bread.
Bon appétit.
I love it.
Croquette.
Korokke (croquette)
Sour.
No way... this smells like delicious almond milk. Mmm... Which one do you want to try? Almond milk. It tastes just like almond milk.
Second one.
Wow!
So many cars!
Delicious!
Mango Frappe
I still have one syrup left today.
I'm heading this way!
Rust!
Let's go for the last one!
Let's go for it!
But if I write, if I write...
Rust! It's hard!Rust! It's so hard!
It's so hard!
Potato!
Oh! Potatoes!
Looks so good!
Yanbai Muscle!
Looks like consommé.
Yummy?
Oh, it's Pak.
No pak?
Bye-bye.
Oh, it's beautiful.
Shopping center.
Julia.
I have really nice skin here.
It's so leaky!
It's not very beautiful, but it leaks a lot! Very beautiful skin! Isn't it beautiful?
Why? It's normal.
It's super clean.
The lights are beautiful.
So what's for dinner?
What's for dinner?
Wow.
Cute little pre-papetino.
Yay.
Cute.
It's adorable.
It's so cute.
Bon appétit.
What do you think?
Apollo.
Apollo in Japan.
Yum! Yum!
It's so good! It's so good!
It's so good!Very tasty!
Super yummy!
Umami! Yum!
Cheers!
Black Piece
Yum!
Oharu, what did you eat?
Ramen!
Ramen?
Delicious!
Indonesian hot bomb ramen.
It was delicious.
It was spicy, but the Indonesian staff said it was about level 5 spicy,
This was the hottest one today, about level 9.
I thought it was really strong.
But it was delicious.
Does it still hurt?
Still hurts.
It still hurts.
I think I'm blushing so much right now.
I'm learning Japanese.
I'm a little calm.
Japanese Jerry
Oh, wow!
He said it's in Japanese.
Oh, that's Japanese!
That's too awesome!
Japanese food!
Wow!
The bill!
I bought a lot!
Yes, so today is
Night of the 2nd day
Today is the second night! This is the second night since we arrived yesterday.I am in the middle of the night! I came yesterday and it is the second night.
This is the second day since I arrived yesterday. Today I spent the whole day doing interviews and various photo shoots.
I had a lot of fun from morning to night.
Everyone was so kind and it was a lot of fun! And it was so fresh and new.
There were so many motorcycles and cars on the streets.
I spent a very enjoyable and fun day, experiencing a different atmosphere from that in Japan. So, today, after work, I went to a party....
Ta-da! I bought some souvenirs!
And I bought it at a supermarket!
Let me introduce them to you!
First of all, here's a flakka!
I think I saw a youtube of some Indonesian food on youtube.
I thought it looked delicious, so I bought it.
And here's Nutella, which I bought because I thought it looked good.
I think we usually eat it with this, but I'm really curious about what's in it.
Julia bought a lot of Nutella.
And speaking of coffee in Indonesia, here it is!
Jay Jay Royal coffee! Ta-da! J.G. Royal coffee!
I bought the most popular coffee called Toraja!
And this is also coffee.
This is also a coffee, but it is a little bit expensive.
The nutrition of this animal is very good.
It is a sweet coffee without sugar.
I was curious and bought it.
Is this coffee unique to Indonesia?
I don't think I would have bought it if I hadn't come here.
I bought it as a commemoration of my visit to Indonesia.
I am looking forward to drinking it.
And here it is.
Miso soup.
And look. It's spicy.
I don't think so in Japan.
I don't have an image that miso soup is spicy.
This is spicy!
And, oh, yes, yes, coffee!
I heard that it tastes good with this chocolate in it.
A little bit sweetened...Or sweeten it a little.
I bought a lot of different kinds of chocolate.
I also bought one that has 70% cocoa chocolate in it, and I also bought one that has 70% cocoa chocolate in it.
And today I went to Starbucks and bought these absolutely delicious, absolutely hard, crunchy cookies!
And look at the candles! Look at these cute vertical candles! Look! Look at those cute little vertical candles! Vertical candles!
Vertical and also this one.
I bought these candles that smell great!
Look! Smells so good! Pink! So cute!
I bought pink and these long thin candles.
And here!
I bought some whitening toothpaste.
My dance teacher gave it to me as a souvenir when she went abroad a long time ago.
It makes your teeth wider.
She bought me some toothpaste, and I found it, so I bought another one!
Yeah, I don't know what it tastes like. I think this one is mint, but I don't know how to drink this one, so here it is.
So I will enjoy Indonesia when I get home!
Tomorrow is the third day!
I'm going to do my best on the third day, too, because I'll be doing various interviews and shadows all day long.
So, after Healin takes a bath, Kanalin will take a bath, too,
I have to learn a difficult dance for tomorrow, so I'm going to do it.
See you all soon. See you tomorrow!
you